http://www.realbeer.com/shared/privacy/index.php

- Oktoberfest
Competition results:
- Great American Beer Festival
- World Beer Cup
Privacy Policy
At Real Beer, we think the Internet should be fun and we want to help you enjoy it. Our privacy policy was designed with that in mind, to respect and protect the privacy of our users so that they may comfortably enjoy Real Beer sites. We want you to fully understand how we collect information from you and how we use it.
These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving. Any changes in policy will be posted on this page. If the changes represent a material departure from our current philosphy with respect to the use of personal information, the changes will be posted here 30 days prior to taking effect and will be included in Real Beer Page Mail.
Use of email addresses
Real Beer collects email addresses from users who want to receive various newsletters we publish. These email addresses will not be sold, traded or otherwise given to a third party. Each message you receive from Real Beer will include information why you are receiving it and clear instructions on how to unsubcribe from the list.
Use of IP addresses
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're connect to the Internet. Real Beer collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, possible troubleshooting, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When guests request pages from Real Beer, our servers log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. However, our discussion boards will display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message.
Use of cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find them at most major websites, but at Real Beer we minimize their use.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.
Links to other sites
Real Beer provides links to sites outside the Real Beer Network. These sites may have different privacy policies -- they may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Real Beer's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Real Beer's control.
Discussion forums
Real Beer offers users the opportunity to participate in forums, or message boards. Any information you disclose when posting a message in these forums becomes public. Those who post a message in our forums make their email address available to others through a feature of our forums software, which could result in unsolicited email from other subscribers or parties. If you contribute to a discussion board you will be asked if want the program to remember you. If you answer yes a cookie will be set that makes posting messages easier in the future.
Compliance with legal process
We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Real Beer on the Internet; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.
Beer.edu • Community • Fun • News • Breweries & Pubs • Search • Contact Us • Privacy Policy • Subscribe
© 1994-2018 Real Beer Media, Inc.
